LIKE FATHER LIKE DAUGHTER
Come on!
Come on, Papa, keep going.
It takes more than a fall and a snowstorm
to stop an Iop and his favorite daughter.
But the snowstorm, it's trying
its hardest. It won't get us, though.
I promise, I'm going to find us
a cozy place to take shelter.
Hold on, Papa.
Just hold on a bit longer.
Elely!
Stop with this nonsense
and show yourself!
Come on.
I promise I won't hurt you.
Papa!
I thought you were dead.
I mean, only for a minute.
I know that nothing can kill you.
And... Eva?
Mama and Flopin were taken by Adamai
and the fat Pandawa is catching us up.
I... I'll take care of him.
You're all beat up, Papa,
you can't even stand up.
-I've got this.
-You... You're too little.
"An Iop is never too young
for a good fight."
Just don't forget to use your head.
That's the first thing you taught me!
Come on, little girl, stop hiding!
A great destiny awaits you!
Yeah, and a good beating awaits you!
Once I'm done with you, tell me
where my mom and brother are.
Young ones...
You should rest, little sister.
No, I'd rather stay here with him.
Father might remain in this state
for months and we have a kingdom to rule.
Can't you have the decency to wait
before thinking about ruling?
I'm thinking of our people. Someone
must be there to make decisions.
Isn't it just perfect
that someone is you, Armand?
-You've been waiting for your moment.
-I've spent my life preparing for this.
But when will you start
behaving like a queen?
So you're still fighting,
even at my bedside?
Sorry, Father.
Armand is right, Amalia.
You can't spend your days at my bedside.
Huh! I hate these darn portals.
Yugo!
-Amalia, there's an emergency...
-Shame on you!
Yugo the Eliatrope, you think
you can go wherever you like,
This is the Sadida king's bedroom!
Our father, the beloved king, is sick!
What right do you have
to burst in here uninvited?
Sorry. I didn't realize.
That's enough, Armand!
Yugo has saved the Sadida Kingdom
several times.
-He is one of us.
-Father!
What has happened to you, Yugo?
You look quite distraught.
It's Adamai. He...
He's back and he attacked Dally,
Eva and the kids.
I'm scared Dally is no longer with us.
No longer with us?
That's impossible! You're talking about
your brother and our best friend.
I saw it all, Amalia.
We need to go and check.
I can't go right now.
I need to stay with Father.
Oh, no, you don't!
As king, I order you
to go and help your friends.
It's time the Sadida Kingdom paid
its debt to the Brotherhood of the Tofu.
Come to my room, Yugo,
and explain the situation.
Get well soon, Your Highness.
It looks like I'll get
a break from all the arguing.
Come on, little girl.
You can't be serious.
You're not really going to fight me,
are you?
You know, I'm the child of a god, too.
We should join forces, not fight.
You should have started with that
before you destroyed our house.
Well, maybe we got off on the wrong foot,
but it did save us some time.
And we have big plans
for you and your brother.
It's not up to you to decide what we do.
That's what our parents are for.
I see. As stubborn as an Iop. You won't
come without a good spanking, I get it.
It'll take more than a spanking,
fat furball!
You have bad manners, little one.
You need to be taught a lesson.
That's how naughty little girls
get disciplined.
-You're fast.
-You ain't seen nothing yet, girlie.
In an open space like this,
I can do whatever I like.
In your house, I wasn't at my best.
What a lousy excuse! Just because
you won't admit you were humiliated.
Listen, pipsqueak, every time
you disrespect me, you'll get a spanking.
You'll get tired before me, you big dummy.
Is that all you've got?
Okay, he's fat, but faster than me.
On the other hand, it looks like
he needs a running start.
You warming up yet?
Yeah, in this weather,
that's a good thing!
Another one, then?
My pleasure.
Well, you fat furball, how does that feel?
You little pest, you'll pay for that!
Okay, fine!
I won't treat you like a kid any more.
It's about time, fatso!
Elely!
What am I now?
An Iop who's no longer an Iop.
Not able to defend his own family.
Come on, Dally, you're better than this.
We're in the same state,
good for nothing.
Speak for yourself, Iop head.
What? This place...
No! Am I really dying?
Looks like it. It was bound to happen.
You're not a god anymore.
Yeah, but no way! Not now of all times.
I can't leave Eva and the kids
to defend themselves.
Sometimes, we don't get to choose.
Nobody chooses when they go.
That's life!
Stop this madness, Rubi!
It can't end like this, not now!
Well, I wouldn't hold your breath.
You saved me once, you can do it again!
First time was an accident.
I didn't know what I was doing.
Don't forget I'm a Shushu.
Okay, Rubi, cut to the chase
and tell me what you want!
You know very well what I want, Iophead.
A nice new sheath, maybe?
Or for me to sharpen you more often?
To think I once thought
you were less of an Iop than you looked.
Honestly, I don't know.
My freedom, moron! I've been locked up
in this sword prison for years.
Let's make a new pact.
I help you, and you free me.
I'm your guardian,
I'm not allowed to free you.
If you'd rather claim your place
in one-armed Iop heaven...
Rubi, after all
we've been through together,
you wouldn't let me go like this!
Is that it?
Is the spanking really over already?
You asked for it.
An Iop should know how to use her head!
The first thing my dad taught me!
I thought you were a little pest,
now I'm sure of it!
A sneaky little pest.
I see why Adamai is so intent
on you joining the brotherhood.
You'll make an excellent Iop goddess.
You said, Iop goddess? Yeah, whatever.
I wasn't dreaming.
It really happened.
-Do you really think that Adamai did this?
-I saw him, Ruel.
Over there.
Did they fall down there?
Nobody could survive a fall like that.
Dally isn't just anyone, Amalia.
Okay. That's it, then, I'm not dead.
Now I just have to find my daughter.
Huh? What the heck is that?
You can't knock that Pandawa
around without your favorite arm.
-Rubi, this... this is great!
-You ain't seen nothing yet.
You can transform it
into any shape you like.
Since we're connected now,
just let me know.
But it's no excuse to be an idiot!
Rubi, this is better than great, it's...
Superb?
-Is that better than great?
-Yeah!
It's superb, then!
Just don't forget our deal.
I help you and I'm free.
A promise is a promise, Rubi.
Elely!
-Papa? Are you done napping?
-I'm coming, sweetie. I'll take care of...
Forget it!
You are going to let me finish my fight.
-You look like you're in bad shape.
-Well, look at him!
Sir Percedal? I thought you were dead.
We Sadlygroves are hard to get rid of.
Okay, but finish him off quickly.
We need to find your mom and brother.
Finish me off?
Did you fall on your head...?
Look, Papa!
My hands are too small to punch him!
I'm doing what you said
and using my head.
Okay, make sure you use your forehead,
or you'll hurt yourself.
-Like this?
-All right!
I... I've had enough. I... I give up.
What do you mean, you give up?
Is he allowed to do that, Papa?
Well, it's rare. He's a wimp, that's all.
Is that a victory for me,
or do I need to off him?
It counts as a victory!
And we don't off people in this family.
Yeah, except he deserves it.
You can't be serious. Sir Percedal!
You need to settle this one yourselves.
I'm still not strong enough to stop her.
Dally!
I thought you were dead!
Whoops! Sorry. Wait, are... you crying?
With pride, Yugo.
I just watched my daughter
win her first fight.
Dally!
But... did you got your arm back?
Sure did, I made a pact with Rubi
just before I died.
He helps me find Eva and Flopin,
and I free him.
Hold on, you mean he actually saved you
in exchange for his freedom?
Exactly!
Dally, you do know
that when a guardian dies,
his Shushu is finally freed, right?
Yeah, so what?
Oh, uh... No, it's nothing.
Rubilax only saved you
because he's a big ol' Shushu softie!
Open your trap again, Grandpa,
and I'll show you how soft I am.
Oh... I'll be quiet.
Dally, was it really Adamai
who attacked you?
He was unrecognizable,
physically and "montally..."
"Metally..." What I'm trying to say is,
he wasn't in his right mind.
Fortunately, we've got someone here
who can tell us how to find my brother.
It's no use threatening me, Yugo.
I won't tell you a thing.
No need for your life story.
We've heard quite enough from you!
Just what we were looking for.
Recall potions.
These are going to take us
where we need to go.
I need one to get back.
Count yourself lucky you're getting off
easy. Ready for the next chapter, sweetie?
Fists will fly, Papa.
Let's knock some teeth out!
Are you ready to face Adamai
after what he did?
There has to be a reason, Amalia.
I know Ad and I can't believe he'd attack
Dally and Eva unless he was forced to.
Someone's got to be pulling the strings.
We'll need to watch over him again,
Amalia.
Let's go.